Hello Gas, we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard, this company's
quarterly result for 2023 has been
announced, so how was the result of this company, that is what we are going to
discuss in today's video.
Talking about ICICI General Insurance,
talking about Lombard General Insurance, this
company has announced its quarterly result here, the
entire amount has been
mentioned in the results, we will
talk about it here, how has the company
performed, this is the result of the scooter,
this is the result of the last quarter and this is the
result of the same quarter of last year, if we
talk about the revenue from here, then the total income
of the company from the premium income is
seen this quarter at
₹ 493 lakh, above the quarterly border
and compared to the quarter of last year, the
income of the company is growing well, if we
talk about the experience of this company, then the total increase is
seen in this quarter, the
quarterly result is ₹ 3 lakh 982 lakh, above this and
compared to the quarter of last year, the
expenses of the company are also increasing here.
Talking about the net profit of the company, the net profit seen in this quarter is Rs
5953 lakh on a quarter-on-quarter basis
and compared to the quarter of last year, the
company's results are
seen improving excellently, which is a
very positive thing. If we
also talk about the earnings per share of the company, the
running series of the scooter of the company is
seen to be 12.03, which
was Rs 7.11 in the previous quarter and the
result of 9.11 in the previous quarter has grown excellently.
Everyone will see here that the company has
decided to give money as dividend in the entry here.
Look at the final dividend, there is a big
mistake here. Inside the result, you will
see that it is written above the final dividend
that a dividend of ₹5 will be given, but this
thing here is wrong. Actually, the
dividend here is here  The
company is going to give a division in the form of a divide in the entry
and that dividend
amount here is ₹450 seed, okay, so the
announcement of this five rupee dividend here is wrong, it has been entered
here by mistake, otherwise this
company has announced a dividend of ₹450, if we
talk about its record here, then the
record date is seen as 28 October
and the pay date of this company's dividend is
seen here as 16 November, okay, so the
record date is on 28 October and the
PF date of this company's dividend is on 16 November, okay, now let's
also
talk about what should be done in this company, by buying from here in the company's SIM, by the way,
after seeing this result,
you can buy this communication on the occasion of buying,
look inside this company, I seem to be in a mood to
buy this company right now,
because
even above the level you  People can buy. If you have
invested from a very high level, then you can
do that also if you want to buy in this company above the current level. Rest,
in this communication, there is a very
good support zone of Rs. 117 here, you
can buy above that. Friend, yes, but there are
opportunities to buy at all these levels like 1040 or 820. If you want to do the middle one, then
this is the first support of 1260 here
which is the resistance and you can keep the target
above these two levels of 1370 in the short term. If we
talk about the medium term targets, then from here the
level of Rs. 1528 and the
level of 1695, these levels are
going to be medium term here in communication.
Okay, so I have told you the short term and medium term
targets as well as the
support. Right now, if
you want to invest here and
hold for the long term in this company, then you
can do it in this company. Okay, that's all
for today. Like the video.  If you come then don't forget to like and
subscribe to the channel. Goodbye,
goodbye, see you again in the next video.
This was our view regarding this company.
Please do tell me your opinion
in the comment section. Okay, goodbye, goodbye, see you again
in the next video.